<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-03T18:40:25-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Iconic Sports</title><subtitle>Zesty Yeung group project displaying iconic players, teams, moments in sports</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Baseball Sandy Alcantara</title><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Alcantara.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baseball Sandy Alcantara" /><published>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Alcantara</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sandy Alcantara is the Miami Marlins’ ace pitcher. He started his career with the St. Louis Cardinals before signing with the Marlins in 2018. While his numbers over the years have been slightly above average, his 2022 season has been stellar. He pitched 6 complete games with an ERA of under 2.5. with a WHIP under 1, he is in the running for the NL Cy Young Award.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baseball Julio Rodriguez</title><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/JRod.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baseball Julio Rodriguez" /><published>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/JRod</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julio Rodriguez is a 21 year old center fielder for the Seattle Mariners. The 2022 season was his rookie season, and he was a sensation. During Spring Training, he earned his spot on the opening day roster, and from then onwards he did not look back. The rookie was productive for the Mariners, as he got on base a lot as well as motivating the team. Some say that he was the catalyst the Mariners needed to clinch a postseason berth for the first time since 2001.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baseball Aaron Judge</title><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Judge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baseball Aaron Judge" /><published>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Judge</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge is a Right Fielder for the New York Yankees. Known for his slugging, he is one of the only players to have multiple seasons where he hit more than 50 home runs. in the 2022 season, he broke the record for the most home runs in a single season in American League History, smashing 62 home runs. He carried the Yankees offense on his back when they were undergoing a slide in the month after the All-Star Break. With a historic season, Judge is a frontrunner for the American League MVP Award.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baseball Manny Machado</title><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Machado.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baseball Manny Machado" /><published>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Machado</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manny Machado is a 30-year old third baseman who plays for the San Diego Padres. He is known for his stellar defense and timely hitting. Ever since he took the field as a Baltimore Oriole at the age of 17, he has been a sensation. He homered in only his second career game, and played insane defense. Before signing with the Padres, he was known as “the villain of baseball” for the aggressive and bully-like manner in which he played. In 2019, he signed a 10 year, $300 million deal with the Padres, and he was given the role as a mentor. Several people have noticed his growing maturity and the way he puts the Padres on his back.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baseball Albert Pujols</title><link href="https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Pujols.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baseball Albert Pujols" /><published>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://rohanagr.github.io/FrontendRepository/2022/11/03/Pujols</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Albert Pujols was a DH / First Baseman for the St. Louis Cardinals, the Los Angeles Angels, and the Los Angeles Dodgers. He played his final season with the Cardinals in 2022, coming full circle. He also breached the 700 career home runs mark, totaling 703 in his legendary 21-season career. During the All-Star Break, no one expected him to breach the 700 home run mark, but he started hitting home runs regularly during the months of August and September. He was a major factor in the Cardinals’ postseason push.]]></summary></entry></feed>